Finding Aid for the Program for Art on Film Records, 1951-1999, undated IA20008
Institutional Records and Archives
- Program for Art on Film and Production Laboratory records, 1971-1999; (bulk 1984-1994); Series I.; 67 Linear Feet; (circa 71 boxes)
  - Legal documents, 1985-1999; Series I.H.; 4.17 Linear Feet; (4 boxes)
    Records consist of correspondence, transcripts, contracts, legal documents, release forms, and reports created for and used by the Program for Art on Film and its Production Laboratory, 1985-1999. The records document the legal activities behind the production of the various Program for Art on Film film projects (including Art on Film/Film on Art), including arrangements for screenings and distribution, and work with consultants; and provide information on the joint venture arrangement between the Metropolitan Museum of Art and the J. Paul Getty Trust, the collaboration with Pratt Institute, sales of Program for Art on Film publications, and publishing information.
    See also Series I.C. Art on Film/Film on Art and Series I.H. Production Laboratory miscellaneous information.
    - Legal files:
      - Consultant Contracts, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Model Contracts: Consultants, 1990-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Consultant Contracts (Getty forms), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Model Contract (DB: Data Acq.), 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - British Film Institute (BFI): contract, 1986; 1993,; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Nat'l Film Board of Canada (NFBC): contract, 1992-1994; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - CCUMC/Bowker re EFL (Locator): contract, 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - AG Kunstlerfilm (G. Minas): contract, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Telco Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Cuadra/Star Software MTNCE Agreements, 1986-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Cuadra Assoc. Computer SW/HW Purchase Agreement, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Film/Video Storage: Bonded, 1995-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Prod. Lab Masters/MOMA (on deposit), 1994-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Academy Film Archive (Prod. Lab films donated), 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - VPRO re Prod. Lab: agreements /correspondence, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Lease Extension/980 Madison, 1990; 1992,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Joint Venture Proposal, 1982 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Joint Venture Contract, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Joint Venture Contract, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Joint Venture Contract, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Joint Venture Agreement (MMA/JPG), 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Lab Films: Study Guides (contracts, correspondence, etc.), 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Database Searches, 1985; 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Consultants: Agreements, Invoices, 1984-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-118)
      - Signed Releases: J. Sternburg Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Koninck/Anamorphosis, 1990; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - (N.C.) Development, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Pratt Agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Inventory: Rights and Permissions, 1990-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Promotion: Releases, Permissions, 1991-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - ERIC, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Mitch Block: correspondence re, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Legal: Counsel's Office and Roper and Barandes, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Eric Roper Legal, 1985-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Legal: Copyright and Trademark Applications, 1992-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - ISSN info. and applications re Art on Screen and Close-ups, 1992; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - UNET2 Technologies, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Getty Pubn. Services re PAF titles/royalties, 1994-1999 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Photo Book: Getty sales reports, 1991-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Photo Book: Sales/MMA, 1991-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Photo Pubn. Contract w. Basia, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Art on Screen (G.K. Hall/MacMillan) Royalty Reports, 1990-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - G.K. Hall Contracts, 1990-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - MacMillan Publishing: Credit Memorandum, 1992; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Art on Screen: Authors, Contracts for Essays, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Architecture on Screen: Authors, Contracts for Essays, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Consultant Agreements, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
      - Consultant Agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-121)
    - Production Lab, legal:
      - Inventory and Log-out sheets, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Requests to Screen Lab Films, 1989-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Contact sheets: Filmmakers and Art Experts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Prod. Lab Masters and Copies (Deliverables), 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Delivery Dates, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Film Lab Letters, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Transcripts of Films (Prod. Lab), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Art on Film/Film on Art Transcript, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Music cue sheets, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Lab Film Copyright, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Copyright Information, 1989-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Sample production contract, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Production Agreement/Legal Contracts, 1987-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - PAF/PL Legal, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Legal Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - [Untitled: Legal documents], 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - PAF/PL Legal, 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Production Insurance, Release Forms, etc., 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-96A)
      - Release Forms, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Art Object Releases, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Release Forms: For Interviews, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Misc. Production Info, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Production Laboratory, Miscellaneous, 1988; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Fan Mail Production Labs, 1985-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Production Consultants, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Marketing and Education Consultants, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Lab Film Distribution, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - AFA Distribution, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - PTV/Lab Film Anthology, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - "Lab Films: Festivals", 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
      - Interview Questions: S. Morris, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
  - Production Laboratory miscellaneous information, 1986-1996; Series I.I.; 3.13 Linear Feet; (3 boxes)
    Records contain financial documents, transcripts, public relations materials, legal documents, correspondence, and inventories relating to the Program for Art on Film Production Laboratory, 1986-1996. The records provide additional information, beyond the administrative, legal and financial, on the day-to-day operations of the Production Lab, such as the results of evaluations and focus groups, and information on film distribution.
    Records of the Production Laboratory are scattered throughout the subseries. See also Series IG. Legal records.
    - Production Lab Information:
      - [J. Paul Getty Trust Bulletin Fall 1992 (multiple copies); Art on Film/Film on Art folders (multiple copies); binder with information on program film deliverables; Evaluation of Anthology Themes for Program for Art on Film, 1991 (multiple copies)], 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Development Budget and Cost Wraparound, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Prod. Lab Film Evals, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Prod. Lab Film Evals (2), 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Focus Group Art Experts, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Focus Group "In House", 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Conversation Transcripts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Conversation Transcripts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Focus Group: Summary, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Video Anthology: Press Screening, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Lab Film Evaluation (Adams and Goldbard Interviews), 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - AoF/FoA Press Kit Originals, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
      - Eval of Lab Films, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-101)
    - Production Lab files; feature film information:
      - Joan Shigekawa: Consultant, 1986-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Prod. Lab: J. Sternberg, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Production Lab Capital Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Interoffice Memos, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Du Art Laboratories, 1989-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Lab Films: Distribution, 1989-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Lab Films: Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Lab Film Evaluations, 1988-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Lab Film Inventories, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Prod. Lab Films: Printouts and Addresses, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Distribution, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - P.L. Distribution: BBC and RM, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - NHK/HDTV conversion of lab films, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Home Vision: Video Anthologies, 1991-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Distribution of P.L. Anthologies: Home Vision, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - PMI/Home Vision, 1992-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Home Vision Contract, 1990-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Art on Film/Film on Art Promo, Comps, etc., 1991-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Video Anthologies, Delivery to Recipients, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Annotation Style, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Feature Reviews to Enter, 1990-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Features to be entered, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Master Copies, 1988-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Feature Length Narratives, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Feature Length Narratives, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
      - Feature Reviews to Add, 1992-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-111)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1994; Series I.J.; 2.19 Linear Feet; (7 boxes)
    Records consist of press materials, letters, worksheets, surveys, reports and brochures produced and collected by and for the Program for Art on Film, 1971-1979, 1984-1994. These records support the activities documented in the preceding series, such as the reports on film and video and the articles used for research and development; many are not original materials, i.e., records produced by the Program for Art on Film. Others are blank copies of surveys and forms that provide no contextual information, or correspondence that contains no contextual information. Included are miscellaneous materials not created by the Program for Art on Film but used for administrative purposes.
    - Research and Development:
      - Genre and Form Headings, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Geographic Attributes, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - AHIP: Vocab. Coord. Group, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Inventory: International Contacts, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Transparencies, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Indexing Worksheet, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Record Formats (samples), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Genres, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Authority Files: Other Orgs., 1985; 1989,; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Harriet Harrison: Consultation, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Database Design: Quality Control, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - PAF Info. Sheet, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - User Profile, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - DB Users Survey, 1989-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - DB Survey Results, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Telephone Survey of Non-Subscribers, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Telephone Survey of Database Users, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - Telephone Survey of Evaluation Panelists, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-98A)
      - [Reports], 1981; 1985,; 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-99B)
        [Telephone Research on Art Institutions Producing Film and Video, August 31, 1985; Art on Film Database Access Survey, Institution Report; Film and Television and the Metropolitan Museum of Art: A Proposal for the Future, April 8, 1981 (2 copies); Art on Screen Newsletter, 1992; Needs Assessment; Needs Assessment Vols I, II, III.]
      - Article in The Independent, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-102)
      - Children's Films on Art, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-115)
      - The Arts and Media (articles, research, etc.), 1988-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-115)
    - Miscellaneous materials:
      - November 1984 CA. Trip, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-25A)
      - Data Entry Form, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-102)
      - Evaluation Forms, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-102)
      - Masters of Articles, 1971-1979 (Box 2004.IA.14-115)
      - Warranties, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-123)
      - Copy Machine: Ricoh, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-123)
      - AV Equipment: Manuals, Warranties, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-123)
      - [Miscellaneous financial], 1989; [American Express information; Independence Savings Bank information.] (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
- Records collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1951-1998; undated; (bulk 1984-1994); Series II.; 51.8 Linear Feet; (45 boxes, 3 framed posters, 2 flat files)
  These records are organized into eight subseries:
  Series II.A. Information on American film production and distribution companies and organizations, 1971-1998 and undated (bulk 1984-1994)
  Series II.B. Information on international film production and distribution companies and organizations, 1972-1997 and undated (bulk 1984-1994)
  Series II.C. Information on films, 1974-1996 and undated (bulk 1984-1994)
  Series II.D. Information on film-related conferences, 1982-1997 and undated
  Series II.E. Subject files, 1965-1998 (bulk 1980-1990)
  Series II.F. "People files", 1960-1996 and undated (bulk 1983-1996)
  Series II.G. Film festival files, 1959-1998 (bulk 1984-1997)
  Series II.H. Visual materials, 1985-1995 and undated.
  Records consist of correspondence, memos, catalogs, brochures, inventories, press releases, clippings, photographs, articles, printed materials, resumes, programs, posters, books, films, magazines/journals, CD-ROMs, slides, and reports collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1951-1998. The bulk of these records were used to compile the Art on Screen ("Critical Inventory") database.
  The records describe American and international companies and organizations that produce and distribute films on art; individual films (both feature and documentary) that take as subject artists or art; conferences where films on art were screened; and miscellaneous informational materials. Much of this material is promotional in nature (catalogs, brochures, and press releases).
  The "Subject Files" (labeled as such by Program for Art on Film personnel) describe artists, films, organizations, projects, art historical time periods and movements, and such diverse topics as art education, attitudes towards films, international television markets, and management.
  The "People Files" (labeled as such by Program for Art on Film personnel) describe artists (both contemporary and deceased, working in a variety of media), filmmakers, art historians, and other individuals with interest in film and/or the arts. Some of the individuals represented in the records served as evaluators for the Program's publications (including its films).
  The records contain information in the form of catalogs, brochures, programs, and other printed matter documenting film festivals. These festivals, both national and international, were concerned specifically with films about art.
  The visual materials comprise posters, slides, and image-oriented interactive visual arts software. The posters included in the records are generally advertisements for films; also included are photographic images of two projects by the artist Christo.
  - Information on American film production and distribution companies and organizations, 1971-1998; Series II.A.; 10 Linear Feet; (23 boxes)
    These records are listed first, by subject matter, and second, alphabetically.
    Records consist of catalogs, brochures, inventories, press releases, clippings, photographs, printed materials, correspondence, and reports, collected by the Program for Art on Film, 1971-1997 and undated, that describe American companies and organizations that produce and distribute films on art. Much of the material is promotional in nature (catalogs, brochures, and press releases). The bulk of the records are printed materials; any correspondence found within the records contextualizes these records, and is often in response to a direct query by Program for Art on Film personnel. Some of the information was used to compile the Art on Screen ("Critical Inventory") database.
    - Academic and Entertainment Video, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Adler Video Marketing, Ltd., 1989; 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Agency for Instructional Technology, 1989-1994; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - AIA American Institute of Architects, 1992; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - AIMS Media, 1987; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Alarion Press, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Albert Kahn Gardens and Collections, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Almi Libra Cinema 5, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Alternative Filmworks, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Ambrose Video Publishing, Inc. (Time-Life Films), 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - American Craft Council, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - American Federation of Arts Film Program, 1987-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - The Annenberg/CPB Collection, 1993-1994; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Appalshop, 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Archives of American Art, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Argos Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Art Com, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Artcivi Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-22)
    - Artmedia, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Artist's Video Productions, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Art/New York [see inner tube], 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - ArtsAmerica, 1990-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Arts for Television, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - The Arts on 4, 1983 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Arts Management Programs: NYU and Columbia University, 1988-1989; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-11B)
    - Art Today, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-1A)
    - Attica Cybernetics, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-17)
    - August Light Prod., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Baker and Taylor, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Balfour Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Barr Films, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-8A)
    - Baseline, 1988-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Beacon Films, 1993-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Benchmark Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Berlet Films, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - BFA, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - BHA, 1986-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Billy Bud Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Black Filmaker Foundation, 1983; 1985,; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Michael Blackwood, 1989-1991; 1993,; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Blackhawk Catalog, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Bluehorse Films Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Boston: Museum of Fine Arts, 1971; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Brighton Video, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Britannica Films/Video, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Brooklyn Public Library Film Catalog, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Buffalo State College Film Library, 1983-1986; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Bullfrog Films, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - California Newsreel, 1991-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Cambridge Career Products, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Cambridge Documentary Films, Inc., 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Camera Three, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Arthur Cantor, Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-52B)
    - Canyon Cinema, 1969; 1972-1973,; 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Carnegie Museum of Art, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Carousel Film and Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Castelli-Sonnabend Tapes and Films, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Center for Humanities, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-57A)
    - Centre Productions, Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Centron Films and Video, 1984-85 (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Churchill Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cinebar Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-22)
    - Cinecom, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - The Cinema Guild, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cinema Libre Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cineworks, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cine-World, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Circle Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Circle 8, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - City Lore, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Clearvue/eav, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Coast Community (Castline), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Coast-to-Coast, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Coe Film Associates Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Concepts Unlimited Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-49)
    - Contemporary Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Corinth Films, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Corning Museum, 1983 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Coronet Film and Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Creative Arts Television Archive, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - CRM/McGraw Hill, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - CRIZMAC, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cross Current Media, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Crystal Productions, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Cunningham Dance Foundation, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-49)
    - Cunningham Dance Foundation, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Deep Dish TV, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Delphi Research Inc., 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Delphi Research Inc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Direct Cinema Limited, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Discovery Channel, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Walt Disney, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Distribution 16, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Documentary Educational Resources, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Downtown Community TV Center, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Drew/Fairchild Communications, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-22)
    - E, 1988-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-60A)
    - Educational Video Network, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Eidos, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - EMME Interactive, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Enc. Britannica: See Britannica [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Ergo Media Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - ERN: Leonardo Project, 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Evergreen, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Expanded Entertainment, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Facets Video, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-21)
    - Fanlight Productions, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - FIDM Museum Library, 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Film Images/Radim, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Filmfair Communications, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Filmakers Library Inc., 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Film-Makers' Cooperative, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Film Orgns.: Misc., undated (Box 2004.IA.14-9)
    - Films for the Humanities, 1983; 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Films Incorporated [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Films Incorporated, 1984; 1988,; 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Films Incorporated [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - First Run/Icarus Films, 1993; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - First Run Features (see First Run/Icarus), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Florida State University, 1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Flower Films, 1985-1986; 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)
    - Focus Media, Inc., 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-53)